
Rule: Application Process Unavailable (unexpected)
Rule: Application Process Shut Down (Inactive)
Rule: Agent Instrumentation Disabled
Rule: Corrupted PurePath(s)
Rule: Truncated PurePath(s)
Rule: Timed Out PurePath(s)
Rule: Application Process Out-of-Memory
Rule: Continuous transaction recording was aborted
Rule: Test Violation
Rule: Custom Events
Rule: Deployment
Rule: High Overall Failed Transaction Rate (Inactive)
      Measure:       Failed Transaction Percentage 
	  Severity:      severe 
	  Aggregate:     avg 
	  Metric:        Failed Transaction Percentage 
	  Operator:      and
      Type:          Measure
      Desc:          
	  Upper Severe:  3.0
Rule: High Overall Failed Page Action Rate (Inactive)
      Measure:       Failed Page Action Percentage 
	  Severity:      severe 
	  Aggregate:     avg 
	  Metric:        Failed Page Action Percentage 
	  Operator:      and
      Type:          Measure
      Desc:          
	  Upper Severe:  3.0
Rule: Average response time degraded
Rule: Response time degraded for slow requests
Rule: Failure rate too high
Rule: Application Process Unhealthy
Rule: Host CPU Unhealthy
Rule: Host Network Unhealthy
Rule: Host Disk Unhealthy
Rule: Host Memory Unhealthy
Rule: Host Availability